popisle.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy - POP Isle

**Company Practices**

The following statement describes the overall company practices of PopIsle Ad Network, including advertising on our network of websites, and products and services that are offered by PopIsle Ad Network. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PopIsle Ad Network does not own or control, or to people that PopIsle Ad Network does not employ.  
Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data  
PopIsle Ad Network delivers advertisements across multiple channels and media, including to web surfers who visit any of the hundreds of websites that are a part of PopIsle Ad Network’s network. With respect to individuals who visit those sites, we, and/or one or more of our third party advertising technology vendors, may collect what is known as “Click Stream Data.” Click Stream Data is anonymous, and includes information such as a web surfer’s IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us or a third party advertising technology vendor. We, and/or a third party advertising technology vendor, may use different types of technologies to collect this type of information, including cookies and web beacons (1×1 pixels).

**How Collected Information is Used**

The non-personally identifiable data that PopIsle Ad Network and/or its third party advertising technology vendors collect are used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements to people across the different websites they visit. PopIsle Ad Network may also use the non-personally identifiable data to better target content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The data are also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. If a consumer elects to provide PopIsle Ad Network with personally identifiable data, we may utilize such data for marketing purposes. In addition, that data may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to that consumer’s preferences and behaviors, and for other PopIsle Ad Network sales and marketing efforts.

**Personally Identifiable Consumer Data**

PopIsle Ad Network uses ad serving technology from Cox Digital Services. Personal information is collected from PopIsle Ad Network publishers to establish a business account. Publishers should refer to the Cox Digital Services Privacy Policy for more information.

**Sharing with Third Parties**

All personally identifiable data provided by individuals is maintained in confidence by PopIsle Ad Network. There are instances, however, in which personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. The non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of PopIsle Ad Network on an anonymous basis. In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that PopIsle Ad Network, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. If that’s the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information. Finally, PopIsle Ad Network may share information on individuals as it deems necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.  
Third-Party Advertising Technology Vendors  
PopIsle Ad Network also works with various third party advertising technology vendors. Although the majority of the online advertisements on PopIsle Ad Network sites are displayed by PopIsle Ad Network, we also allow third-party ad serving companies, including other ad networks, to display advertisements on our sites. These vendors may also use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect Click Stream Data. These companies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting based on their cookies, and some of them are also members of the Network Advertising Initiative. You may find more information by clicking on the company names above and following the links to the Web sites of each company.

**Security Precautions**

PopIsle Ad Network and it’s advertising technology partners make significant efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure the high security standards. Any data that is stored on PopIsle Ad Network’s servers is treated as confidential and is not generally available to the public. PopIsle Ad Network has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating our security measures does exist.

**Consumer Choice**

Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data – Use of Cookies & Opting-Out PopIsle Ad Network uses technology, including technology from its third party advertising technology vendors, which include cookies and web beacons (1×1 pixels), to deliver better, targeted marketing messages to the web surfer. These tools are used to collect non-personally identifiable data to provide better and more relevant services and messages to that user. We believe that the use of such tools assists in providing a more meaningful web-surfing experience, but you may opt-out of the use of PopIsle Ad Network cookies and those of our third party advertising technology vendors if you would like. To do so, you can disable cookies on your browser.

**Miscellaneous**

A Special Note About the European Union European Union web surfers understand and consent to the processing of personal information in the United States.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

The issue of privacy is an evolving one. PopIsle Ad Network is committed to the constant monitoring and examination of its privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any material changes are made to the company’s privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this privacy policy that discloses the changes.

**Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy has been in effect since December 24th, 2015.

**Contacting Us**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding PopIsle Ad Network’s Privacy Policy, please contact us, or you can send correspondence to the following address:

CONTACT  
180 Brodie Dr, Unit 5, Richmond Hill  
ON L4B 3K8, Canada  
General info: manager {@} popisle {.} com
